http://www.odawacasino.com/general/privacy.php

Stay Safe Together!
Last Revised: 12/15/16
Odawa Casino  values customers like you and respects your privacy. The Privacy Policy pertains to Odawa Casino  and the Odawa Casino website. Odawa Casino does not sell, trade or rent any personal or non-personal information to outside unauthorized parties.
Collection of Personal Information
Odawa Casino collects the personal information you provide voluntarily at Odawa Casino and the Odawa Casino website. This also includes information provided by postal mail, telephone, email, Facebook , Twitter and other means. Personal information collected through the Odawa Casino website may include your name, date of birth, postal address, email address, telephone number, fax number and gender. Confidential Personal Information, such as credit card information, gaming activity, hotel reservations, driver's license and driver's license expiration date is also collected.
Collection of Non-Personal Information
Web browsers or authorized third party services associated with Odawa Casino may collect non-personal information pertaining to your visit(s) to the Odawa Casino Resort website. The non-personal information may include a unique identifier assigned to your server, internet connection, geographic location or movement within the Odawa Casino website. Non-personal information is gathered to generate statistics about visitors on the Odawa Casino website.The Odawa Casino website utilizes "cookie" technology. A cookie (also known as a tracking cookie, browser cookie, and HTTP cookie) is a small piece of text stored on a user's computer by a web browser. The Odawa Casino website uses cookies to collect website statistic data, such as web pages visited, downloaded material, your internet provider's domain name and country, and the addresses of websites immediately visited before and after visiting the Odawa Casino website. When the situation permits, non-personal information may be linked to personal information.
Marketing Purposes
Personal information and non-personal information may be used for Odawa Casino's marketing purposes. Marketing purposes includes notifying you of promotions, offers and events via postal mail, email, telephone, Facebook, Twitter and other means. Odawa Casino reserves the right to share your personal and non-personal information to authorized third party services associated with Odawa Casino and the Odawa Casino website; however, Odawa Casino does not permit the use of confidential personal information for marketing purposes.
Non-Marketing Purposes
Odawa Casino and the Odawa Casino website may use your personal information, including confidential personal information, to respond to inquiries, comments or complaints, processing and fulfilling of hotel reservations and Players Club memberships.
Opt-Out Instructions
By deleting your recent internet cookies or configuring your web browser to reject the use of cookie data, you opt-out from Odawa Casino  collecting your non-personal information. You reserve the right to opt-out of the use of your personal information for marketing purposes by notifying Odawa Casino. Please call 1-877-442-6464 (local: 1-231-439-6100), complete the Contact Us form on the Odawa Casino website (indicate opt-out request within the "Comments" field) or write to:
Odawa Casino
Attn: Marketing
1760 Lears Rd.
Petoskey, MI 49770
Persons Under Ages 19 and 21
Odawa Casino and the Odawa Casino website are intended for those 19 years of age and older. Certain restrictions at Odawa Casino are applied to those under 21 years of age. We reserve the right to verify your age at any time, for any reason, and may refuse admittance or service to a person who does not have a valid government pictured identification at any time while at Odawa Casino.
Privacy Policy Revisions
Odawa Casino reserves the right to revise this Privacy Policy at any time without notice. Revisions made to the Privacy Policy will only apply prospectively to personal information or non-personal information collected or modified after the effective date of the revised policy. If you have any questions regarding the Privacy Policy, please use the Contact Us form.
About Odawa
877-442-6464
Promotions Schedule
Event Calendar
Property Map
Connect with Odawa
About Odawa
877-442-6464
Enjoy and relish the sounds of music right here at Odawa Casino. Take a look at our featured artists and events.
Book Your Escape
Get away from it all and make Odawa Casino your destination for gaming, fine dining, and nightlife.
Group Packages
Great rates are available from motorcoach groups staying at Odawa Hotel, starting at just $79 per night!
